<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<books>
    <Book>
        <Title>Country of the Blind</Title>
        <Author>H.G. Wells</Author>
        <Text>In one of H. G. Wells's most brilliant and haunting stories, Nunez, a hapless mountaineer falls several
            thousand feet down the side of an Andean mountain to find himself in the Country of the Blind, a sealed-off
            valley, where, for fifteen generations, a strange community of congenitally blind human beings has been
            thriving in complete ignorance of the outside world. Nunez gleefully reminds himself of an old proverb:
            "In the Country of the Blind, the One-Eyed Man is King," but, to his dismay, things do not happen quite
            as he had hoped. The Country of the Blind was written in 1904 and first published, in book form,
            in 1911.
        </Text>
        <ISBN>1-86092-002-0</ISBN>
        <Genre>science fiction</Genre>
        <PublishDate>1911</PublishDate>
        <Cover>hard</Cover>
    </Book>
    <Book>
        <Title>Arthur Savile</Title>
        <Author>O. Wilde</Author>
        <Text>Lord Arthur Savile's Crime, first published in 1887, opens at Lady Windermere's society soire in London.
            A chiromantist, Mr Septimus Podgers, has been brought to the party to entertain the assembled guests. All
            goes well until he examines Lord Arthur Savile's hand: "Podgers grew curiously pale, and said nothing.
            A shudder seemed to pass through him. Then some huge beads of perspiration broke out on his yellow forehead,
            like a poisonous dew, and his fat fingers grew cold and clammy...."
        </Text>
        <ISBN>1-86092-016-0</ISBN>
        <Genre>classic</Genre>
        <PublishDate>1887</PublishDate>
        <Cover>soft</Cover>
    </Book>
    <Book>
        <Title>Little Tale</Title>
        <Author>R.L. Stevenson</Author>
        <Text>This gruesome story was first published in the Christmas issue of the Pall Mall Magazine for 1884 and,
            although it had been written some time earlier, Stevenson initially laid it aside "in justifiable disgust,
            the tale being horrid." One night Fettes, an old Scotsman at the George Inn, is shocked out of his
            drunkenness by the sudden appearance of a shady figure from his past, Dr Wolfe Macfarlane. The sight
            of Macfarlane brings back terrible memories for Fettes, in particular, the nightmarish events of that
            stormy night in a rustic graveyard at Glencorse.
        </Text>
        <ISBN>1-86092-001-2</ISBN>
        <Genre>detective</Genre>
        <PublishDate>1884</PublishDate>
        <Cover>hard</Cover>
    </Book>
</books>